let quiz=[
    {
      question: "A cuboid shaped wooden block has 6cm length, 4cm breadth and 1cm height. Two faces measuring 4cm * 1cm are coloured in black. Two faces measuring 6cm * 1cm are coloured in red. Two faces measuring 6cm * 4cm are coloured in green. The block is divided into 6 equal cubes of side 1cm(from 6cm side), 4 equal cubes of side 1cm(from 4cm side). How many cubes will have green colour on two sides and rest of the four sides having no colour :",
      option: [
           "8",
           "24",
           "16",
           "4",
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "If A is substituted by 4, Bby 3, C by 2, D by 4, E by 3, F by 2 and so on, then what will be total of the numerical values of the letters of the word SICK :",
      option: [
           "11",
           "12",
           "10",
           "9",
      ], 
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many times can you subtract 10 from 100 :",
      option: [
           "9 times",
           "10 times",
           "1 time",
           "0 times",
      ],
       answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "A number of cats got together and decided to kill between them 999919 rats.Every cat killed an equal number of rats.Each cat killed more rats than there were cats.How many rats do you think that each cat killed :",
      option: [
           "1009",
           "991",
           "2000",
           "1000",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the missing number in the following puzzle -> 2+3=8, 3+7=27, 4+5=32, 5+8=60, 6+7=72, 7+8=?? :",
      option: [
           "86",
           "98",
           "104",
           "112",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "How many letters of the word FAINTS, will their order in the word and that when the letters are arranged in the alphabetical order, remain the same :",
      option: [
           "Two",
           "One",
           "Three",
           "Nil",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "In a certain country 1/2 of 5=3. If the same proportion holds, what is the value of 1/3 of 10 :",
      option: [
           "4",
           "6",
           "8",
           "10",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Solve the math puzzle given below, If 3=5, 5=3, 7=4, 8=6, 10=7, 11=8, Then 12=?? :",
      option: [
           "14",
           "10",
           "9",
           "8",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Solve the math puzzle given below -> If 2=3, 3=8, 4=15, 5=24, Then 7=?? :",
      option: [
           "36",
           "40",
           "48",
           "60",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Solve the following equations and find the value of product of a,b,c -> If a+b+c=6, a2+b2+c2=14, a3+b3+c3=36 :",
      option: [
           "3",
           "6",
           "9",
           "12",
      ],
      answer: 2 ,
    },
    ]
    